What are the three most important traits that
you look for in people when you're assembling
like a leadership team or employing people for a company?
Well, I think you have to work with honest people.
You have to work with intelligent people.
And you have to work with
people that they can take constructive feedback.
And that includes yourself.
And I think...
You got to be like coachable.
Yeah, I think that's critical.
And you're not always going to get along.
Our wives at the time, in our first
early days of the founding of the company, they
thought my partner and I were going to
kill each other because we were constantly arguing
and constantly...
But what we were doing is really fleshing
out the best path forward or the best idea
forward.
And I remember in the early days, we
had some horatious arguments over which shade of red
we were going to make
our first packaging on our product.
And it turned out to
be this inconsequential kind of thing.
But eventually, through that process, we became
closer and closer friends and trusted each
other more and more to make independent decisions.
And we needed to go through that early on
to order get to that level of confidence with
each other.